

AZZAZ ABDELHAKIM

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

azzazhakimou@gmail.com

+213 779991468



github.com/hakim-az



linkedin.com/in/abdelhaki m-azzaz-27194a1b3/



azzaz-abdelhakim.netlify.app

FRONT-END SKILLS

- CSS 3
- SASS
- BOOTSRTRAP 5
- TAILWIND CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT JS
- NEXT JS
- NODE JS

DESIGN SKILLS

- ADOBE XD
- ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR
- FIGMA

LANGUAGES

- Arabic Native language
- French C1
- Enalish B2
- Spanish A2

ABOUT

I recently graduated in computer science with a specialization in information systems and software engineering. Currently a student in the second year of a Master's degree in Computer Networks and Embedded Systems.

I'm also a Front-end Developer with 3 years of experience building and maintaining responsive, modern and animated websites. Proficiency in HTML/CSS/JavaScript as well as modern libraries and frameworks (React Js).

EDUCATION

High School Degree - Mathematics

El Mokrani High School | 2016 - 2019

Bachelor Degree - Computer science

Algiers 1 University | 2019 - 2022

Master Degree - Computer science

Algiers 1 University | 2022 - 2024

EXPERIENCES

ALL VIBES AGENCY

Front-end Developer | 2019 - 2021

SONALGAZ (stage pratique)

Front-end Developer | 02/2022 - 06/2022

ALGERIA PARTNERS

Front-end Developer | 01/2023 - 06/2023

INFINITY AGENCY

Front-end Developer | 07/2023 - Today

FREELANCE

Front-end Developer | 05/2021 - Today